

Gauray Shukla

ASP .NET MVC/Windows Developer

Phone: +91-9815-854-851

Address: #23, Ravindra Enclave Ph-2, Balatana, SAS Nagar Mohali, Punjab-140603

Email: gauravshukla1409@gmail.com

I am proficient in C#, ASP.NET, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, MS SQL and have extensive experience with windows application development. My attention to detail, communication, meeting deadlines, quality work, effective problem-solving and time management skills have proven beneficial to various software and systems development projects for business in such areas as healthcare, maritime, retail and logistics.

EXPERIENCE

VERIFAVIA Shipping

Nov 2018 - Present

Software Developer

- Serve as project manager to build custom tools for Client, Operator and Ship management.
- AIS API Integration to fetch the record of Vessel's movement.
- Designed Web-based ASP.NET Internet applications linked to firm-wide SQL databases.
- Worked on varies conversion tools like DOC to EXCEL, PDF to EXCEL, EXCEL to EXCEL and XML to EXCEL to achieve some internal task for the organization.
- Develop proprietary solutions to automate customer invoicing regarding services like EU-MRV, IMO DCS and IHM projects.

Inteq Infocom

Jan 2018 – Oct 2018

Software Developer

- Developed enhancements to enterprise Purchase order/Sale order planning Web-based .NET application for leading maritime organization.
- Designed and reviewed Excel to Database import tool, analyzed software development process and suggested good methodology to achieve the task.
- Liaised with production team to analyze bugs and resolve issues.
- Worked with Heidi SQL databases and designed stored procedures.

NeolTsoft Solutions Jan 2015 – Dec 2017

Software Developer

- Participated in system specification meetings, analyzed user requirements, coordinated with coders and team members.
- Worked on retail invoice management software which is used to keep track of stock and invoice.
- Served as project manager to build a tool for toll plaza to manage vehicle's toll tax.
- Implemented new features and applications into existing websites.
- Designed and created an application which monitors the progress of the order, track client production SLA's and reconcile client transmissions to actual production for invoicing.

EDUCATION -

Panjab University

August 2010 - July 2013

Graduation (BCA)

CBSE Board

August 2009 - July 2010

August 2007 - July 2008

Higher Secondary

Punjab Board

Matriculation

• .Net C#

SKILLS

- JavaScript, HTML, XML, CSS
- Knowledge of Networking
- Working knowledge of WordPress
- Database knowledge of SQL Server Management Studio 2008 and above
- MySQL, Heidi SQL
- Excellent interpersonal and communication skills, including good presentation and report writing skills Self-motivated and lifelong learning attitude
- · Ability to work to deadlines, underpressure
- Strong analytical skills
- Excellent troubleshooting
- Punctual

ACHIEVEMENT

- Participation in various competitions at college level.
- I got merit certificate in academic session.

LANGUAGES

Hindi (Full professional proficiency) **English** (Full professional proficiency) **Punjabi** (Full professional proficiency)

HOBBIES

- Poetry writing
- Gardening
- Listening to Bollywood music